你看到我從天上飛過
You see me soaring through the sky
我看到你從地上走過
I see you below as you walk on by
我只要十秒就能清光雲層
I could clear the sky in 10 seconds flat
厲不厲害
Well, how about that,
厲不厲害？
well, how about that?
我可以坐在雲上好好放鬆
I could be sitting here on a cloud,
看著太陽緩緩下山
watching the sun as it starts to go down
現在只缺一個人
The only thing missing
那就是你
is you by my side
給我來些自信心
Give me a smidge of confidence
給我來點有意義的話
Give me a speck of something that makes sense
讓我來給你依靠
Give me an idea of dependency
讓我來展現忠誠心
Give me a dash of loyalty
忠誠心
Loyalty
我能給你我孤單的靈魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我總是感覺不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以給我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因為你知道我會陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠誠」才是我的座右銘
That's why they call me loyalty
忠誠心
Loyalty
太陽高掛，可卻下了雨
The sun shines bright, yet the rain pours on
彩虹一下來一下又離開
Rainbows here one minute and then they're gone
他們讓我想起了你
They remind me of me and you
你做了什麼？
What did you do?
我做了什麼？
What did I do?
你雙眼裡的決心
Determination in those eyes
他們去哪了？已經消失了嗎？
Where has it gone? Has it said goodbye?
時間過得好快
A lot has happened
可是我會陪著你
but I'll stay by your side
給我來些自信心
Give me a smidge of confidence
給我來點有意義的話
Give me a speck of something that makes sense
讓我來給你依靠
Give me an idea of dependency
讓我來展現忠誠心
Give me a dash of loyalty
忠誠心
Loyalty
我能給你我孤單的靈魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我總是感覺不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以給我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因為你知道我會陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠誠」才是我的座右銘
That's why they call me loyalty
我們在一起時間就會靜止
Time stands still when you're with me
我要怎麼讓你看清
How can I make you see?
你的白目讓我想發狂
Your crazy antics make me want to scream
吼你名字吼到喉嚨爛掉
your name so loud till my throat starts to bleed
爛掉
to bleed
我能給你我孤單的靈魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
總是感覺
the feeling in my heart
你可以給我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因為你知道我會陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
我能給你我孤單的靈魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我總是感覺不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
你可以給我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因為你知道我會陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠誠」才是我的座右銘
That's why they call me loyalty
我能給你我孤單的靈魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我總是感覺不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以給我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因為你知道我會陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠誠」才是－－
That's why they call--
所以「忠誠」才是我的－－
That's why they call me--
我能給你我孤單的靈魂
I could save my lonely soul for you,
但我總是感覺不能接受
but the feeling in my heart can't follow through
不能接受
can't follow through
你可以給我你破碎的心
You can give your broken heart to me
因為你知道我會陪著你
'cause you know that I'll stay with you
所以「忠誠」才是我的座右銘
That's why they call me loyalty